We are next going to hear from Christian
Riza, who's from the he's the Utah chapter
president of Stand with Crypto. And for
those who aren't aware, the crypto
enthusiasts I think are pretty excited
about the decentralized identity approach.
And the Utah Blockchain Association has
gone way out of their way to bring
together stakeholders and even many in
this room that they've been working with
for years to help educate them on SEDI and
bring their support to help make this
happen. Christian.
So I do I represent Stan with crypto. I am
the chapter president for the state of
Utah. And it's my rep it's my
responsibility to represent the 20,000 pro
crypto voters in the state of Utah and
mobilize them on initiatives that really
align with our values. Now, you're
probably thinking, okay, crypto, that has
nothing to do with SEDI. Cryptocurrency
has nothing to do with SEDI. Why are you
here? What does this matter?
Our assets, our finances and our assets
have been digital for years. We've just
never had the ability to take ownership,
to take custody and to have those in our
control. And likewise, our birth
certificates, our social security numbers,
all of these things are already digital.
They live in a database somewhere. We've
just never had the ability to have true
ownership and custody over those pieces of
our identity. Recently, I had the
opportunity to go to our community and
really ask them and have some honest
discussions and a bunch of different chats
throughout the state. And, you know, all
of these people, the crypto and blockchain
people are extreme skeptics when it comes
to this kind of stuff because frankly, you
know, all they know is we want to have
control over our assets, our finances, all
these things. We don't want the government
involved in these things, right? So at
first gut reaction of, hey guys, what do
you think of this initiative? It was, no,
no, what? No, please don't do it. What are
you talking about? Like, no, this is
terrible. And what I did was had everybody
actually dig in and And Will Segos as
well, which is he's here. We had some
conversations in deep, in-depth
conversations with a lot of these
community members and had them really dig
into the underlying protocols. They're
technical people, right? And after having
reviewed the information and the framework
and how it's being proposed, it was an
emphatic yes. And I've got some quotes
here from some of these people, which in
this case, it seems great. It seems too
good to be true. I'm surprised the state
is backing this. Definitely the best
approach that I've seen, this actually
makes sense. I like it. There's no way the
state of Utah would go for it. And my
favorite one, if the state of Utah did
this, I would be proud. I'm not a
policymaker. I don't come from, you know,
I'm not here representing a big tech
enterprise. or anything like that. These
people that we represent are just people.
They're regular Joes, regular community
members, and they deeply care about their
privacy, their control, their ability to
hold these different things, parts of
their lives, their identity, their assets,
and these things. They deeply care about
these issues. And based on the SEDI
framework, some of the things that ACLU
has said, And, you know, the way that SEDI
is structured and framed today, the
community emphatically wants to support
this. And so I guess I'm here to say that,
you know, as a community member, as a
person that represents people in the
community, you know, if you move forward
with SEDI in this way, the state of Utah
and other states that are here represented
that will support that. And we hope that
you will. So, thank you.